(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-23T13:56:53.872525",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Gawr Gura 3D LIVE
水面に映る自分が言った
My reflection in the water said to me,
「ああ、私は悪いサメです」
"Oh, I'm such a bad shark."
ずっと恐れていた
I'd been so terrified all this time.
赤く光るその目 海の底暗闇に消えていく
Her glowing red eyes begin to sink into the void at the bottom of the sea.
どうして 泣くのか
Why do you cry?
欲しいものなら全部手に入れた 教えて 私は望んでいた私になれたかな
I gave you everything you craved. Tell me, could I become the me I wanted to be?
嘘はつけない でも本当じゃない 骨は言わない 楽じゃない
No lies, but no truths either... Isn't it easier to never say what you really mean?
いつかは どこかで 分かち合える時が来るの
Will the time ever come when we can understand each other somewhere?
look at this so-called "gem of the sea"
odd and scrawny, don't you see what I mean?
return to what you know, it ain't much I know
ずっと追い求めた
I've been searching and searching
私なりの答え 自分には
for my own answer, and I won't...
ek lógou állos ek vaí nei lógos
One word brings another...
水面に映る ジブンが言った
My reflection in the water says to me,
「あぁ、わたしは 悪いサメです」
"Oh my god, you're such a bad shark."
ずっと恐れていた
Her terrifying gaze,
赤く光るその目
her glowing red eyes
海の水底
begins to sink into the void
暗闇に消えていく
at the bottom of the sea.
どうして (your tired eyes)
Why (your tired eyes)
泣くのよ (begin to fall)
do you cry? (begin to fall)
欲しいものなら 全部手に入れた
I gave you everything you craved
教えて (your darkest thoughts)
Tell me if (your darkest thoughts)
私は (unleash them all)
I can ever be (unleash them all)
望んでいた 私になれたかな
the me you wanted me to be
嘘はつかない でも本当じゃない？
No lies, but no truths either
本音は言わない方が楽じゃない？
Isn't it easier to never say what you really mean?
いつかは (a time and place)
But someday (a time and place)
どこかで (for darker days)
Somewhere (for darker days)
わかりあえる 時が来るの？
Will we find someplace to understand each other?
さようなら
Farewell
ありがとう
Thank you
隠していた 私はもういない
I won't hide my heart's desires anymore
さようなら
Farewell
ありがとう
Thank you
すべて受け入れて 生きていくから
I'll accept my everything and live
海の底は つまらないけど
The bottom of the sea is a boring place
あなたのことは 忘れないから
But I'll keep you in my thoughts forever
いつでも (no matter where)
No matter when (no matter where)
どこでも (watch over me)
No matter where (watch over me)
私らしく 生きていこう
I'll live life true to myself
oudén kakón amigés kaloú
Nothing bad is without something good
Thrilling! Is this love?
[Title: Thrilling! Is this love?]
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah!
ねぇ 歌うわ
Hey now, here is my song
そうよ あなたに
For you, yeah, that's right
甘たいけれど 恥ずかしいかもね
I wish that I was yours, but I'm too shy
願いごとの呪文、ほら ムニャムニャムニャ
If only I could just conjure a spell...
(かーもね！)
(I suppose!)
ずっと このまま 時が止まらぬ かもね
Then, you and i would be together
(かーもね！)
(I suppose!)
こういうのが 恋なの
Is it love that makes
ドキドキドキッ！
my heart go "boom, boom, boom"?
しかもね、かもね！
And what's more... I suppose!
スキスキスキッ！
Love you, love you, love you!
昨日よりも… かもね！
More than yesterday... I suppose!
ねぇ 歌わせて
Hey now, sing it to me
そうよ あなたも
That's right, I'm talking to you
乙女の気持ちが 伝わるといいな
I hope that this message finds you well
(いいな！)
(Wonderful!)
夜からで そんなくらい
I just can't hold it back anymore
もう ラブラブラブユー
Yeah! Love you, love you, love you
ずっと このまま あなた素敵が いいな
If only we could stay just like this
(いいな！)
(Wonderful!)
こういうのは はじめて
I never felt like this
ドキドキドキッ！
My heart going "boom, boom, boom"!
あぁ いいな、いいな！
It's wonderful!
スキスキスキッ！
Love you, love you, love you!
さっきよりも… いいな！
Even more than before!
Hi! Welcome to the Gumba's official first ever 3D live concert! Yeah!
Hi! Welcome to Gura's official first-ever 3D live concert! Yeah!
I have a lot to show you today.
And we have a lot of guests to sing with as well, so I'm gonna need you to stand up and let's get this party started! Woo!
日本のファンも来てくれてありがとうございます。いつもサポートをしてくれるのが嬉しいです。
Thank you to all my fans in Japan for coming. I'm so happy you always support me.
First of the stage, for the first time ever, Reflect Jazz flavor.
First on stage, for the first time ever, "REFLECT" (Jazz flavor).
My first song ever, I wanted to give it a special new touch just for you. Uh, it's a little different from the original, but...
I really like it. Chad-ified.
Maybe I'm biased, though, but I hope you enjoyed it regardless.
How do you like this stage, though?
Mite, mite. Look! Look at this Ebio over here.
Look, look! Look at this Ebio over here.
Looking so suave, you know.
And how many fish can you spot, hmm?
There's quite a few. There's, uh, royal blue tang and then there's yellow tang.
And I'm sure, I'm sure you guys know all about your fish, right? All your fishes?
And I'm sure you guys know all about your fish, right? All your fishes?
Of course you do.
I got to say, though, all this dancing is making me hungry, and all this fish talk is making me hungry, mungry.
I guess it's time for guests then, no?
Ikuyo!
Let's go!
森羅万象の悪戦苦闘も
Even the toughest trials in the world
マヨネーズかけたら大体美味しくなる
Will taste good if you add mayonnaise
君が泣いてもお腹は空くよ
Even if you cry, you'll still get hungry
消化できなかった「ごめんごめん。」
Couldn't digest it, "Sorry, sorry."
酸いも甘いも勝手に食べて
Eating whatever sour and sweet things I want
ご迷惑おかけしております
Sorry for causing you so much trouble
パクチーなーおきで 変な味のジュース
Cilantro arrangement, weird-flavored juice
心を無にして飲み込みます
Ignoring my heart, I gulp it down
ああ 混沌 情報多めのレストランで
Ah, at the restaurant, chaotic information overload
嘘っぱちのメニューにお茶こぼして
Spilled my tea on the lying menu
君と もぐもぐ
With you, mogu mogu
銃撃戦の真ん中で もぐもぐ
Right in the middle of a firefight, mogu mogu
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ 満腹になる未来を願っているよ
Group of starving mountain demons, hoping for a future where I'm full
もぐもぐ 世界が終わる前に もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu, before the world ends, mogu mogu
やみい マジ神 やむやむ ありのまんま
Yamii, godlike crazy, yamyu yamyu, just as you are
もぐもぐ やみい magic coming この世を味わうんだ うまうま
Mogu mogu, yamii magic coming, tasting this world, yum yum
理論武装のミルフィーユサンド
Theoretically backed mille-feuille sandwich
匿名希望のオーロラソース
Anonymous aurora sauce
大雑把な味付け 多めに見諸よ
Roughly seasoned, but overlook it
美味しくなったら「おっ か おっ か。」
If it's tasty, it's ok, ok.
良いもん 悪いもん いっぱい食べて
Good things, bad things, eat lots
汚れた口元拭います
I'll wipe my dirty mouth
おにぎり ピザ ケーキ 豪華なフルコース
Rice ball, pizza, cake, extravagant full course
罠を疑い 気を付けます
Questioning if it's a trap, I'll be careful
ああ 妄想流言飛語のバイキングで
Ah, wild ideas, groundless rumors of a buffet
毒入りと絶品料理より分けて
Sorting between poisoned food and high-class cuisine
君と もぐもぐ
With you, mogu mogu
デスゲームの教室で もぐもぐ
In a death game classroom, mogu mogu
魑魅魍魎 ハラペコの群れ 仲の良い君と生き残れたらいいな
Group of starving mountain demons, it'd be nice if you, my good friend, would survive
もぐもぐ 数年後もこの場所で もぐもぐ
Mogu mogu, in a few years at this place, mogu mogu
やみい マジ神 今夜の晩ごはんは
Yamii, godlike crazy, tonight's dinner will be
もぐもぐ やみい magic coming 次はお前の番だ
Mogu mogu, yamii magic coming, next time will be your turn
もぐもぐ やみい マジ神 やみやみ ありのまんま
Mogu mogu, yamii, godlike crazy, yum yum, just as you are
もぐもぐ やみい magic coming この世を味わうんだ
Mogu mogu, yamii magic coming, tasting this world
うまうま
Yum yum
もぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐもぐ
Mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu mogu yummy
Okayu-senpai, thank you for singing with me.
This is a dream come true.
I could cry right now.
Gura...
I am so happy, too. Thank you.
Actually, I have something to tell you.
Huh? What?
At home, I have some cats to tell you. They are all good...
ぐらをペパー
Gura and Pepper...
Heh, really? That makes me so happy!
Yes, I am a big Gura otaku.
What? I'm an Okayu otaku too!
相思相愛ですね。
Mutual feelings, huh?
But after that, that song! I am a little hungry.
What food do you like, Gura? I'm pretty hungry too!
もぐもぐもぐ... I really love salmon. What do you like?
Munch, munch, munch... I really love salmon. What do you like?
Oh, I like fish and... shark fin?
おかゆ先輩！
Okayu-senpai!
But I am so happy for you, Gura! Congratulations, amazing!
あ、ありがとう、おかゆ先輩！ I'm so happy to have a chance to sing with you.
Ah, thank you, Okayu-senpai! I'm so happy to have a chance to sing with you.
It's what fun seeing singing with you. Let's sing together again soon.
It's so much fun singing with you. Let's sing together again soon.
Yes! Oh no, dad. No more time. I'm living back.
Yes! Oh no, dad. No more time. I'm leaving back.
No, no, no, ちょっと待って！おかゆよ... Can I pet your tail? おかゆ先輩！
No, no, no, wait a second! Okayu... Can I pet your tail? Okayu-senpai!
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ぼいんぼい～ん
Chi-chi-chi-chi oppai, boin-boin!
もげ もげ もげ チチをもげ！
Moge, moge, moge, tear off those boobs!
もげ もげ もげ チチをもげ
まうぎぷりいんぽよんもげ ぼうぎぽらろんぷよんもげ
Maugi purin poyon moge, bougi poraron puyon moge!
まんまるちっちー さんかくおぱーい ろけっとぼいん
Round chi-chi-chi, triangular oppai, rocket boin!
やさしく (もげ!) いきなり (もげ!) 微妙に (もげ!) 連続 (もげ!)
Gently (moge!), suddenly (moge!), subtly (moge!), continuously (moge!)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ぼいんぼい～ん
Chi-chi-chi-chi oppai, boin-boin!
もげ もげ もげ もげ チチをもげ…もげ！
Moge, moge, moge, moge, tear off those boobs... moge!
もげ もげ もげ チチをもげ
Moge, moge, moge, tear off those boobs!
もげぽよよんぱいんもげ もげぱいんぽいんもげ
Moge poyoyon pain moge, moge pain poin moge!
しましまちっちー おさるのおっぱい ばずーかぼいん
Striped chi-chi-chi, monkey's oppai, bazooka boin!
今日も (もげ!) 明日も (もげ!) とにかく (もげ!) 毎日 (もげ!)
Today too (moge!), tomorrow too (moge!), anyway (moge!), everyday (moge!)
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ぼいんぼい～ん
Chi-chi-chi-chi oppai, boin-boin!
もげ もげ もげ もげ チチをもげ…もげ！
Moge, moge, moge, moge, tear off those boobs... moge!
「ははははは、待て待て待て！」
"Hahahahaha, wait, wait, wait!"
「うふふふ、つかまえてごらん！」
"Uhufufu, try and catch me!"
「よーし、つかまえたー！」
"Alright, caught you!"
「いやん、そこはボインよ」「はははははは」
"Iyan, that's boin there!" "Hahahahaha"
チッチッチッチ おっぱい ぼいんぼい～ん
Chi-chi-chi-chi oppai, boin-boin!
もげ もげ もげ もげ チチをもげ！
Moge, moge, moge, moge, tear off those boobs!
シオン、またね？
"Shion, see you again?"
Thank you for coming, Gura!
きたよ！
"I'm here!"
We can sing together again!
呼んでくれてありがとう！
"Thanks for inviting me!"
シオンのライブにも来てくれたよね？
"You came to my live too, right?"
うん
"Yeah."
Oh, that was so much fun!
Me too!
でも本当に暑いね。
"But it's really hot."
うん
"Yeah."
It's very hot, isn't it? Rather sticky. But it is summer, so I guess that makes sense.
Oh, speaking of summer, do you like eating melon? I like big watermelons. They're so juicy and delicious.
"Oh, speaking of summer, do you like eating melons? I like big watermelons. They're so juicy and delicious."
Hey Gura... なんか言いたいことでもあんの？
"Hey Gura... Is there something you want to say?"
でも、夏はいいね。
"But summer is nice."
But summer is nice. I like the beach and eating watermelon too.
"I like the beach and eating watermelon too."
シオンは泳ぐことができるですか？ できるよ！
"Can Shion swim? Yes, I can!"
じゃあ、今度アトランティスに一緒に行こう！
"Then let's go to Atlantis together next time!"
えー！ No way! それは無理！
"Eh?! No way! That's impossible!"
息がそんなに持たないよ！
"I can't hold my breath that long!"
大丈夫、大丈夫、I will help.
"It's okay, it's okay, I will help."
考えとく。はい、OK、It's a promise.
"I'll think about it. Okay, it's a promise."
But now it's time for the next song.
Thank you, Shion!
バイバイ、Gura! バイバイ！
"Bye-bye, Gura! Bye-bye!"
今夜 空港で待ってて
Tonight, please wait for me at the airport
黄昏の空に浮かぶ 金星のすぐそばで
Close by the Venus floating in the twilight sky
ねえ いつかの青い成層圏
You know, that blue stratosphere someday
二人きりどこまでも飛べるかな
Can the two of us fly anywhere together?
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと旅客飛行
Passing a sea of night clouds, a passenger flight 1000 miles away
あなただけの アテンダントの私
I am your exclusive flight attendant,
トリコロール・エアー・ライン
Tricolore Airline
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと旅客飛行
Passing a sea of night clouds, a passenger flight 1000 miles away
あなただけの アテンダントの私
I am your exclusive flight attendant,
トリコロール・エアー・ライン
Tricolore Airline
遥か 異国の空から
From the sky of a distant foreign land
会えないあなたに贈る 絵葉書 恋のエアメール
A postcard sent to you I can't meet—love's air mail
ああ 私ひとり 窓辺で
Ah, I am all alone by the window,
誘導灯の輝きが眩しい
The glow of the taxiway lights is dazzling
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと旅客飛行
Passing a sea of night clouds, a passenger flight 1000 miles away
あなただけの アテンダントの私
I am your exclusive flight attendant,
トリコロール・エアー・ライン
Tricolore Airline
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと旅客飛行
Passing a sea of night clouds, a passenger flight 1000 miles away
あなただけの アテンダントの私
I am your exclusive flight attendant,
トリコロール・エアー・ライン
Tricolore Airline
夜の雲海越え 1000マイル彼方へと旅客飛行
Passing a sea of night clouds, a passenger flight 1000 miles away
あなただけの アテンダントの私
I am your exclusive flight attendant,
トリコロール・エアー・ライン
Tricolore Airline
ぐら、フォーミリオンサブスクライバーおめでとう！
Gura, congratulations on 4 million subscribers!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
You're a famous shark!
本当におめでとう、すごいね！
Huge congratulations, that's amazing!
わーい！ありがとうございます！
Yay! Thank you so much!
稜先輩、マリン先輩、Thank you for coming!
Senpais, thank you for coming!
I'm so excited we can sing together again.
I'm kind of nervous, my heart is beating so fast!
マリンとあくあはどうですか？
Marine and Aqua, how about you two?
Me too, doki doki!
Gura, it was my dream to sing on stage with you.
So I'm really happy to sing at my next live too!
Really? I would be honored, Marine.
わたしも前のライブの時はまだ3Dじゃなかったから
When I had my previous live, it wasn't in 3D yet,
一緒に歌えて嬉しい！
so I'm happy we can sing together!
ねー！
Yeah!
Can I ask a favor?
I want to be eaten by you, Gura!
It depends on what you taste like.
どんな味だろう？
What would she taste like?
Then just Marine-sume...
いいセント！
Smells good!
I hope we have more opportunities to perform together soon.
Please invite me anytime!
いいね！
Sounds great!
Thank you guys for coming today!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
Congratulations! ありがとう！バイバーイ！
Congratulations! Thank you! Bye-bye!
目覚めては繰り返す 眠い朝は
Waking up to a repeating sleepy morning,
襟のタイをきつく締め
tightening the tie around my neck,
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
when I pass through the classroom door...
胸を張って歩き出せる
I can lift my chest and start walking.
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
A wind blows through such an ordinary day.
聴こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it,
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt it in my heart.
震え出す今この胸で
Now trembling in this chest of mine,
もう来る気がした
I felt it coming soon.
幾億の星が消えていくのを
Watching countless stars fade away into the dark,
見送った
I waved goodbye
手を振った
and waved my hand,
よかったね、と
saying, "I'm glad."
廊下の陽見下ろす 掃除の途中
Looking down the hallway while cleaning,
おかしなものだと思う
I think it's such a strange thing—
あたしの中の時は止まっているのに
even though time inside me has stopped,
違う日々を生きてるように
it's like I'm living different days.
埃は雪のように降り積もる
Dust accumulates like falling snow.
待っている気がした
I felt like I was waiting,
呼んでいる気がしたんだ
I felt like someone was calling out.
震え出す今の時が
Now this trembling moment
見つけた気がした
felt like I had found it.
失われた記憶が
Lost memories
呼び覚ました
were awakened—
物語
a story
永遠の
of eternity
その終わり
and its end.
目覚めては繰り返す 眠い朝は
On a sleepy morning when I wake and repeat it over,
襟のタイをきつく締め
I fasten my necktie tightly.
教室のドアくぐるとほんの少し
Opening the classroom door, ever so slightly
胸を張って歩き出せる
I can step out with my head held high.
そんな日常に吹き抜ける風
The wind blowing through such ordinary days—
聞こえた気がした
I felt like I heard it,
感じた気がしたんだ
I felt like I sensed it.
震え出す今この胸で
In my heart that now begins to tremble,
来る気がした
I felt like it was coming.
幾億の星が消えていくのを
I saw off hundreds of millions of vanishing stars,
見送った
saw them off,
手を振った
waved goodbye,
よかったね、と
and said, "Good for you."
待ってる気がした
I felt like it was waiting,
呼んでる気がしたんだ
I felt like it was calling out.
震え出すこの魂が
This trembling soul of mine
見つけた気がした
felt like it had found it,
幾億の夢のように
like a dream of countless eons.
見送った
I saw them off,
手を振った
waved goodbye,
ありがとう、と
and said, "Thank you."
クランク…じゃなくて
Krunk... I mean,
クロニィちは！どうも！
Kronii-chiva! Hello!
どうも！見せてよ！
Domo! Show me!
いやいやいやどう？見せてよ！
Ya ya ya do! Show me!
You do really sound like.
You really sound like that.
Yes, you do.
Um...
Okay.
I've done some improvising.
I was expecting a little bit of hesitation, but I guess improvising, so you're adding to it? Mhm.
I was expecting a bit of hesitation, but since you're improvising, you're adding to it? Mhm.
Yes.
Show me the shoe!
Show me testing.
Thank you for... All right.
Thank you for... Alright.
Thanks for coming and singing with me today.
Oh, no.
Thank you! Thank you!
You're looking mighty magnificent in your, uh, how would I say? Cardboard?
Cardboard? Still taller than you, though.
Oh, I see. Yeah, like you need some growing up.
Well, I literally...
Hey, you're like 95% legs, okay?
But you came out like that.
All legs!
95% legs, 5%...
Okay, you don't have to go that hard.
Anyway.
Okay, spider crab! Wow!
Oh my god, my feelings!
What are you going to do with those weapons? Shishkabab me?
What are you going to do with those weapons? Shish kebab me?
Uh, it's not worth it, but your shrimp friends over there...
look pretty tasty.
Might skewer them.
Hey, leave some for me, if you do.
I'll say though, uh, how do I...
What do I, um, compost or recycle you right now?
Uh, well, you can't. You got to add me...
uh, to the Kronii temple, kind of add it as a limited edition kind of thing?
Right. Right.
Mhm. What if I just hoist you right here and I take you to whatever I find first?
Compost? Recycle? Wait, what? Recycle?
Maybe I'll just put you in my room.
ぴょん、ぴょん、ぴょん、ぴょん、ぴょん、ぴょん！
Pyon, pyon, pyon, pyon, pyon, pyon!
皆さん、ありがとうございました！
Everyone, thank you very much!
Thank you guys for watching! I hope you enjoyed what we prepared for you!
Thank you to my wonderful Senpai for singing with me,
and Kronii-suki, show me desu!
I felt tears welling in my eyes every day I practice for today.
This concert has been one of my dreams come true, and it's all possible thanks to each and every one of you.
最初の日からサポートしてくれてありがとうございました！
Thank you for supporting me from day one!
みんなのメンバーになれて みんなの前で 踊ったり歌ったり 叶えたい夢みたいです
Becoming a member and being able to dance and sing in front of everyone is like a dream come true.
またいつか みんなの前で ライブに立ちたいです
I hope to stand on stage in front of everyone again someday.
その日まで 目を閉じて みんなの素敵な顔を想像します
Until that day, I'll close my eyes and picture all of your wonderful faces.
Now, one more song before we end today!
行くよー！
Here we go!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは 愛のつまった投げキッスで
My repayment is a kiss filled with love!
気のせいじゃない 目は合ってるよ
It's not your imagination, our eyes are meeting!
あと少しって 恋しちゃってください
Just a little more, please fall in love with me!
やれること なんでもします
I'll do whatever it takes!
エナジー出して 代価り頂戴
Give me your energy as payment!
エゴサで見つけたアンチのコメ
The anti-comments I found on ego-searching
ぶっちゃけみんなより分かってるし
Honestly, I know that better than anyone,
でも誕生日 ここに立てばみんながいる
but if I stand here on my birthday, everyone is here.
行くよー！
Here we go!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは 愛のつまった投げキッスで
My repayment is a kiss filled with love!
虜にする！もっと！
Captivate you more!
夢を見せる！もっと！
Show you dreams more!
楽しんでって 愛のつまったスペシャルナイト
Enjoy yourself, a special night filled with love!
ファンサしちゃうぞ みんなありがとう！
I'll give you fan service! Thank you everyone!
お手紙も書いてください
Please also write me letters!
何度も読んで 宝物にします
I'll read them over and over and cherish them as treasures!
すぐやんだり まだ早いけど
It's too early to get depressed,
裏切りません 宣言します
but I promise I won't betray you!
期待や好かれ度には負けない ぶぜんな実力で稼ぐから
I won't lose to expectations or affection; I'll earn it with my raw ability!
だからやめない 負けず嫌い 私はいる
That's why I won't quit, being stubborn, I am here!
行くよー！ こぶし上げて！もっと！
Here we go! Raise your fists more!
汗かいて！もっと！
Sweat more!
恩返しは 愛のつまったサメビームで
My repayment is with a love-filled shark beam!
大歓声！もっと！ まだまだねぇ！もっと！
Big cheers! More! Still not enough! More!
受け止めてね 愛のつまったわがままソング
Catch it, a selfish song filled with love!
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
好きに叫べ！もっと！
Scream however you want! More!
楽しんじゃえ！もっと！
Enjoy yourselves! More!
忘れないで 特別な日になりますように
Don't forget, hoping this becomes a special day!
共に歌おう ずっと！ 共に歩もう ずっと！
Let's sing together forever! Let's walk together forever!
合言葉はとびっきりの Ｌ・Ｏ・Ｖ・Ｅ
The password is an extraordinary L-O-V-E!
好きになって！もっと！
Fall in love with me more!
私を見て！もっと！
Look at me more!
恩返しは 愛のつまった投げキッスで
My repayment is a kiss filled with love!
虜にする！もっと！
Captivate you more!
夢を見せる！もっと！
Show you dreams more!
楽しんでって 愛のつまったスペシャルナイト
Enjoy yourself, a special night filled with love!
ファンサしちゃうぞ
I'll give you fan service!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Gawr Gura 4 Million Subscribers Celebration Merchandise Coming Soon!!!